Filip Lyesovyy

360 St. Paul street, St. Catharines, ON +1(365)880-6610 Lyesovyyf@gmail.com LinkedIn GitHub

10/04/2019

Gibbys Electronics Supermarket Website Developer/Marketer

To whom it may concern.

I would like to express my interest in the Website Developer/Marketer position available at Gibbys Electronics Supermarket. As a current Computer Programmer and Analyst student at Niagara College, I am actively searching for Coop and internship opportunities and I came across this one while surfing my career section at my school's website. As a future graduate I see this position as a perfect opportunity to gain some valuable experience as well as expand my current knowledge.

In my opinion I am a great match for this position since I enjoy being challenged and engage in projects that require me to work outside of my comfort zone and knowledge set. Thus, learning new programming languages, frameworks and simply challenging myself with something new is very important to me. My vast international experience made me a real "outside of the box" thinker as I have seen and experienced things all around the world that simply do not exists anywhere else.

Your listed requirements closely match my background and skills. Also, I would like to highlight some additional skills:

- Great Communication Skills (Both written and verbal)
- Practical experience with Wordpress
- Experience with cloud platforms (AZURE)
- Experience with mobile application development (XAML)
- Experience with full-stack technologies (.Net)
- Practical experience in web application development
- Project management experience in web development

I've attached a copy of my resume that further elaborates on my experience in development. I can be reached any time using the information provided in the header of the page.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to speaking with you about this opportunity.

Regards, Filip Lyesovyy.

Filip Lyesovyy

360 St. Paul street, St. Catharines, ON +1(365)880-6610 Lyesovyyf@gmail.com LinkedIn GitHub

Technical Skills

Front-End	Back-End	uı/ux	Source Control
HTML / XHTML / CSS JavaScript / JQuery XAML BootStrap	SQL / MongoDB C# / ASP.NET/ .Net MVC Python / Bottle /API	Wireframing Prototyping User Stories Accessibility	GitHub/Scrum

Personal Useful Qualities

Excellent communication skills

Confident, articulate and professional speaking abilities. Great public speaker, experienced with presenting various material to large audiences.

Highly Adaptable

Lived in 6 different countries and worked in 4 of them. Can adjust pretty much to any working environment.

Languages

Fluent in 3 languages (Ukrainian, Russian, English), intermediate knowledge of German and basic knowledge of Chinese.

Education

Computer Programmer & Analyst - Niagara College, Welland

Jan 2018 - Current

Program is focused on the full stack development using technologies like Visual Studio where we have been building projects using C# ASP.Net framework, .net MVC, Universal windows applications as well as Xamarin for cross platform mobile development.

Biomedical Science - University of Essex, England

Oct 2014 - June 2016

International Baccalaureate - St. Leonard's Senior school, Scotland

Sept 2012 - June 2014

Filip Lyesovyy

360 St. Paul street, St. Catharines, ON +1(365)880-6610 Lyesovyyf@gmail.com LinkedIn GitHub

Experience

Database Developer - 7Lab-Media

July 2018 – Current

- Part-time remote position
- MySQL queries refactoring and optimization for website's database

Bartender - Niagara College

Sept 2018 – Current

- Preparing beverages for the bar
- Interacting with customers, taking orders and serving food
- Assessing bar customers' needs and preferences, making recommendations
- Maintaining a friendly atmosphere

English Teacher - Yanjiao, Hebei, China

December 2016 - October 2017

- Deliver English classes in public school for kids age of 5-16 years old
- Develop practical and enjoyable lesson plans for the upcoming classes each week
- Provide one to one assistance